Prakash Sellathurai



prakashsellathurai@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/prakashsellathurai



+919361325845



https://prakashsellathurai.github.io

Summary

Experienced and Conscientious Engineering professional with over 2+ years of the proven-track of experience in Computer Vision and Software Engineering.

Delivered Results on early-stage consumer end products and have worked in a cross-functional manner in fastpaced startup environments.

Experience



Software Engineer

GK Fit

Feb 2020 - Apr 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Computer Vision Engineer

Biathinx

May 2019 - Jan 2020 (9 months)

Software Development Engineer Intern

Clothx

Aug 2018 - Jan 2019 (6 months)

Education



SRI KRISHNA COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor of Engineering, Mechatronics, Robotics, and Automation Engineering 2015 - 2019

Licenses & Certifications



Cambridge Business English Assessment - Cambridge Assessment English

HX Exercising Leadership: Foundational Principles - HarvardX

5970feac8bbb4ba2a8c1ce9120fa417c

CutShort Certified Python - Advanced - Cutshort

26222

- CutShort Certified Data Science Basic Cutshort 26226
- CutShort Certified Machine Learning (ML) Basic Cutshort 24979
- Problem Solving (Basic) Certificate HackerRank ef5c7449fac5
- Rest API (Intermediate) Certificate HackerRank 0b4fadc3eadc

Skills

Software Engineering • Computer Vision • Algorithms • Machine Learning • Web Development • Software Development • Agile Methodologies • Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) • Python (Programming Language) • C++

Honors & Awards

Finalist in National level Mobile Robotics Competition - CEG ,Chennai Dec 2016

Kurukshetra is an international techno-management fest conducted annually by the College of Engineering, Guindy (CEG) in Chennai, Tamil Nadu, India. So the team represented our college lead by me went up to the final round and got runner up among the team of 50 across the state.

Core Member in Research and Incubation Cell - Research and Incubation Cell ,SKCET

Mar 2016

Mentored the students on Project Development and creative Problem solving through actively conducting various tec related events that boost the innovation and research activities in the college

Programming Head of SKCET ROBOCON Team - ABU RoboCon

Lead the Team of 30 to build a robot for a nationwide robotics competition among 300 teams across the whole nation and went up to qualifying round